Christopher Brown

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hello there, I go by Chris. I have been a frontend developer for almost two years. I'm interested in all things related to development, frontend to backend. Currently learning more about Redux state management and other headless CMS tools such as Prismic & Wordpress. I have a deep passion for learning & solving problems but a deeper passion for helping others learn.

LOCATION

Address

Clarksville, Tn

- Cbrowndev88@gmail.com
- 270-804-6730
- o chrisbrowndeveloper.com
- in chris-brown-48477b1bb
- ChrisB32-cloud

WORK EXPERIENCE

THE BURGER STORE

WEB DEVELOPER | THEBURGERSTORENASHVILLE.COM

Feb 2021-Present

- Designed & built a full-stack website with mobile first approach that allows the user/admin to change sections of the site that need frequent updates. Site features public & private routing, context API with authentication.
- The goal was to bring awareness to the company & have features where the user/admin can add, update & delete descriptions with uploaded images for a dynamically generated menu. Site also includes a contact form for messaging directly from the site, viewable in admin panel.
- Technology: Next.JS, React, Context API, Sass, Bootstrap, noSQL database, Firebase/Firestore and Firebase/Auth.

INK PRESSIVE

WEB DEVELOPER | INKPRESSIVESCREENPRINTING.COM

Oct 2020-Apr 2021

- Co-designed with another developer & built a full-stack website that is able to handle custom order submissions, upload designs, dynamically generated instagram post, that has public & private routes with authentication.
- The goal was to bring awareness to the company & have features to meet the their needs that include an admin panel for updating weekly promotions & keeping track of order forms. Also be able to update FAQs about their business & services offered
- Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Material-UI, noSQL database, Firebase / Firestore, FireBase / Auth.

LOCAL EVENTS APP

PERSONAL PROJECT | LOCALEVENTS.VERCEL.APP

May 2020-Present

- Created & built full-stack website where users can create & update events details,
 upload event images & add location details on google maps APIs. Features dynamically
 generated events using public & private routing with JWT authentication.
- The goal was to have a website that would allow multiple users to interact with the application to create, update, delete events & also to have and introduction into headless CMS, backend development & SQL databases to improve full-stack development skills.
- Technology: Next.JS, React, Context API, CSS, React-Bootstrap, Node.JS, Express, SQL / Postgres database, Strapi & JWT.

EDUCATION

WEST KENTUCKY TECHNICAL & COMMUNITY COLLEGE

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE IN MATHEMATICS

2014-2016

TOOLS

JavaScript	Rea	eact JS N		ext JS Go		atsby JS		ML	CSS	SASS	JSX	Bootstrap	
React Bootstrap		UI Ma	UI Material		Firebase		Strapi		de JS	Express	Git	GitHub	
filemaker pro													

SKILL SET

Problem Solving	Problem Solving Commu			Resp	onsive De	esign	Mobile Fi			
Functional Program	ООР	OOP ES6 +		Async / Await		Rest API		Context API		
React-Hooks										